{
  "exam_type": "CS",
  "subject": "ANG",
  "questions": [
    {
      "n": 1,
      "question": "A number of people ....... complained about the noise made by aircraft taking off.",
      "options": ["has", "have", "haven"],
      "answer": "have"
    },
    {
      "n": 2,
      "question": "I think ten CFA .......... too much to pay for such a little thing.",
      "options": ["is", "am", "are"],
      "answer": "is"
    },
    {
      "n": 3,
      "question": "The hotel staff ........ not like new manager’s wife.",
      "options": ["does", "do", "has done"],
      "answer": "do"
    },
    {
      "n": 4,
      "question": "More than one house ------- been broken into during the holidays.",
      "options": ["has", "have", "having"],
      "answer": "has"
    },
    {
      "n": 5,
      "question": "------ fool I was not to listen to her advice.",
      "options": ["How", "So many", "What"],
      "answer": "What"
    },
    {
      "n": 6,
      "question": "------ nice to see you!",
      "options": ["So much", "What", "How"],
      "answer": "How"
    },
    {
      "n": 7,
      "question": "Chris was in -------- hurry that she forgot to call you.",
      "options": ["so much", "such a", "what a"],
      "answer": "such a"
    },
    {
      "n": 8,
      "question": "I have to work -------- hard to please them.",
      "options": ["so", "so much", "so many"],
      "answer": "so"
    },
    {
      "n": 9,
      "question": "---------- lovely this is!",
      "options": ["Such", "What", "How"],
      "answer": "What"
    },
    {
      "n": 10,
      "question": "There were ------- people you could hardly move.",
      "options": ["so much", "so", "much"],
      "answer": "so many"
    },
    {
      "n": 11,
      "question": "He has -------- hair on his chest that he looks like a bear.",
      "options": ["so", "such a", "so much"],
      "answer": "so much"
    },
    {
      "n": 12,
      "question": "His admiration for your art is -------- great that he’d pay any price for it.",
      "options": ["such", "so", "how"],
      "answer": "so"
    },
    {
      "n": 13,
      "question": "Don’t forget to take your passport ------- when you leave.",
      "options": ["along", "in", "back"],
      "answer": "along"
    }
  ]
}
